When I was younger, I had a lot of hopes and dreams.
当我更年轻些的时候   我有许多愿望和梦想
You know what? I still do.
你知道吗   我依然有
I wanna keep on learning,
我想要继续学习
discovering.
发现
I wanna keep on working,
我想要继续工作
dreaming.
心怀梦想
I wanna keep on creating.
我想要继续创作
I wanna love and be loved.
我想要爱人和被爱
I'm not gonna lie to you.  I have good days
我不会对你撒谎   我有美好的时光
and bad.
也有糟糕的日子
But I get up every day knowing that I'm the same person I was ten...
但是每天起来我知道我依然和十年
-Twenty... -Thirty years ago.
-二十年   -三十年前的自己一样
And while my body can sometimes get tired or broken,
我的身体也许有时会疲累生病   但
my spirit,
我的精神
my thoughts,
我的思想
and passions
以及热情
remain strong and invincible.
依然是强大且不可战胜的
Because when you get to be my age,
因为你到我这个年纪的时候
-you come to realize I'm still... -Me.
-你会意识到我仍然是   -我